-brandon driesse



Animator - Game Developer

brandon.driesse@gmail.com



Profile

Lover of cartoons and vocal supporter of independent animation and games on the internet through sites like Newgrounds.com. Five years making video games, three years of freelance animating, and twenty or so years of starved passion to create. Hobbies range from tennis to building computers to stop-motion films to photogrammetry to running audio capture on commercial film shoots.

I make stuff; sometimes for money, but always for fun.

Experience

2015 - Present	Creative Director - Scarecrow Arts Independent Game Developer/Publisher Video Production, Motion Graphics, and Developer of Freeware Tools/Scripts for Adobe After Effects
2015 - 2020	The Story Goes On (Steam, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch

J. J. L.	The story sees on (Steam) Abox one, initialize office	٠,
	Initial Release: March 2nd 2018	
	RE-RELEASED: March 2nd 2020	

2018	Newgrounds Summer Animation Jam
	Third Place Winner - Overall
	Four Animations Completed in Six Weeks

2015	intern - Roman Media Group LLC
	Database Organization and Vectorizing Company Assets

2014	SkillsUSA
	Second Place Medalist in the Category of Digital Design

2013 - 2016	Paige - Lilicolli Park Public Library
	Minor Building Maintenance, Light Installation, IT Support,
	Website Management, and Federal Tax Document Filing

Education

2018- Present	Savannah College of Art and Design Junior Year working toward Animation BFA
2015 - 2018	County College of Morris A.A.S. Digital Media Technology
2011 - 2015	Morris County School of Technology Academy of Digital Design